Everyone told me that dreams are a waste of my life
Feeling it coming and knowing that this time it's right
I know that
All that's good will come my way in due time
One more turn, and I'll be set to take  flight tonight.
And we'll go
All day, make all the right plays, in all the right ways
We are the stars of this life
Cut, Break, though it's a tight race,
We'll finish first place
We'll make the best days of our
Lives take more than you know to break
Just know your heart's place
And you will see from new heights
Might take another mistake
But we won't feel hate
Because we know we're flying high
Touring exhibition of the Astral Compass
Here's the crown jewel of this touring exhibition:
The Astral Compass
Believed to possess infinite power
Legend has it, when warrior god Phoenix Master last used it
He disappeared without a trace
Since then
Despite its cosmic importance,
Nobody has witnessed the talisman's magic
How the compass is activated
Has remained a mystery to this day
No way
The Astral Compass has surfaced
In Gold City.
Charge my Rattalion
The talisman is our key to world domination
The Day of Rat- koning is near.
If a counterfeit can't be made from gold
Or silver
The Celestial Master never tasted earthly grub before
What about a compass  made out of dough
I've been pecking at this for 300 years
My beak's worn down!
This pastry compass can fool any deity
I'm sure we'll fool him this time
So forget poop as our Plan B?
Eww!
You gross me out.
We gotta get to Heaven
This is do or die
We only have one shot
At being accepted back into Heaven.
Hail the Celestial Master.
Bottle Deity, for guzzling the elixir. elixir,
You were banished' to earth
My Lord,
I'm Phoenix Master
Oh, you're the Phoenix Master
Aguzzling the wrong elixir
Banished to I Earth.
My Lord you got your deities mixed up
Ah Phoenix!
You abused your divine powers,
Causing harm to mortals
Lost the Astral Compass
Only when you retrieve the Compass.
And attained enlightenment
Can you return to Heaven
You've been with me all this time
Searching the compass for 300 years
Have you found it yet?
If you fail to find it,
Then stay mortal for good
Honestly ,I kinda envy you
I humbly return the Compass
Please examine it
What?
We got busted again
No way!
My handicraft was flawless
It even has mixed -nuts filling
My Lord please check it
Another fake, huh?
Try fooling me with a fake
Then I will strike you with lightning
I'll give you one last chance
Until midnight tonight
Now buzz off
Take your decree with you
Good thing we got flicked, not blitzed.
Hey bruh...
Good thing he only sent one lightning bolt
My bad.
I'll find it before midnight.
I Promise.
Big kite.
Niu niu.
Aren't the Gargoyles on duty?
They're only good for fireworks
Don't expect them to step up to the plate
Freeze demon
Why stick your neck out
I'm greased lightning Ten-ten
I'm Xander the Gargoyle
The city's fearless defender
The righteous Thunder Beast.
You roof- squatting beasts
Can't even scratch me
Easy now!
Chill Bro
I'm Sonny the Pacifier
Brawling is appalling
More convos, less ammo!
Where's Phoenix Master
Is everyone okay?
Master, let's take cover first.
I know the Compass is here
Surrender it
And I might spare your lives
Bruh, take him down!
We're no  match
This is a job for heroic dudes in Heaven.
Gotcha.
Ask Heaven for reinforcements
When did you climb up here?
Ten-ten, have you ever been to Heaven?
Not really.
Where I'm going?
The reinforcements came fast!
The Compass!
My Compass!
Ouch, my eyes!
Rattalion, seize the Compass!
Master,
Can this be the divine warrior?
So that's what a deity looks like
Kitty!
What happened?
This thing kicked the monster's butt
He defeated the Night Demon?
He is so awesome!
Yup, he sure did
Is he a deity from Heaven?
Depends on how low the bar is.
Kitty! Kitty!
Call him the Holy Cat
I saw him crash through the sky.
He must be a holy cat
Holy Cat!
All hail Holy Cat!
Guardian of Gold City
That's one divine dude
Brr...Brr...Bruh!
Welcome welcome!
Welcome to earth! earth!
We welcome you!
Wonder whose mount that was
He came all this way just to bring the Compass back.
We're still in Heaven's good books
They sent an envoy to whup the monster,
And even recovered the Compass for us
Bruh
We're homeward bound at last
Since I got downgraded from phoenix to chicken,
I lay eggs when I get the jitters
You're just chickening out.
You'll be fine once you go back to Heaven
Hey buddy,
These humans worship us
We're a superhero to them.
Cover up the worker's badge
Hide your security guard I cap
Don't blow your cover
And don't let that rat Jerry steal your thunder
Bruh, check out the envoy's crown
I can't decipher the symbols
Officer, since our demotion.
Eh, I mean relocation.
300 years ago
Heaven must have changed a lot.
We're a bit out of touch
Before we return.
Tell us what's trending up there
Bruh
Why isn't he saying anything?
Is he still testing us?
This talisman is da bomb.
Mind your manners
Give it back to our VIP
This weapon is out of this world.
Call me Phoenix Master
Chief of the Gargoyles
I'm honored you've come this far to help
I don't deserve it.
Bruh.
Are you alright?
Meet my mount
A phoenix who loves
Cosplaying as a chicken
Hop on him for a guided tour of Gold City
Followed by a welcoming party
You can Leave this little snack behind.
Sonny, Xander,
Prepare a party
And make sure it's prefect
Copy that, Sir.
Get' ready to party
Today is the Lantern Festival
You grace us with your presence
See this Purple Gold Temple
It's our Gargoyle HQ and watch tower.
Whenever something stirs
We're ready to head out on patrol
This is Golden Lake.
When all the flowers bloom in spring.
The place teems with people
Chang Le Gate
Chang Le Gate and the moat are bulwarks
Against any demonic attack
Gold City is secure under our watch
No demon or monster can broach it
Here is Lantern Street,
The bustling downtown area
Master Cat
You should really be careful
Ouch, that hurts!
The lil'' snack?
The Compass!
Kitty
Hit the breaks!
Holy Cat!
Master's Lantern
Who's this swash buckling hero?
Sheesh, it's a statue of yours truly
The lanterns this year
Are worse than before
The statue's grandeur moved you to tears?
Isn't this a spitting image of me?
Look, the pear blossoms are in full bloom
One can't help but stop to admire them
Bravo!
So you are the new deity in town?
Holy Cat!
Tone down the fanboy stuff.
Meet Jade, my prized pupil.
Didn't expect you to be into Peking opera.
If you're in the mood
Let me sing a duet with you
Commander, watch me
Call me boss!
In broad daylight
We're no  match for him
This furry fellow is a new face
Bravo!
Aunty, which opera are they performing?
Well...
Huh, that's below the belt!
Bravo!
Darn the light!
Boss, leave it up to us
Watch out.
Master cat, it's too chaotic here
It's best I safeguard your compass
Nice hit!
Bruh, it's an ambush!
Bravo!
Take this!
It's a new fusion opera.
'Bugs Bunny vs Daffy Duck.
Bravo!
Thank you. you're too kind
Thank you!
Thank you so much
There's still someone after me.
No, I mean.
The Astral Compass
Bruh, it's already 3pm
I haven't been a very good host
The Lantern Festival is about to commence
Welcome to our banquet
Let's go!
Peach cake!
Fresh out of the oven
I'm the Holy Cat
No! I'm the Holy Cat
Stop right there
Holy Cat paper art!
Candied Holy Cat!
Fun and refreshing
Official limited edition!
Holy Cat portraits!
Best charm to ward off evil
No more bad luck!
Peach cake!
Bless us with feline fortune!
So mighty!
Try our Gold City signature banquet
Dig in!
Wanna be a legend like me?
Better pay your dues first
I'm so cool even Kitty cats wanna date me
I don't know what failure means I never learned that word
I'm talking real life this ain't no Tom and Jerry
Draped in jewels, lounging in palaces-pure luxury
Wherever I go, I'm the talk of the scene
Acting tough, but scared of a mouse
No intro needed-the whole world knows us
My lyrics so hot, they set kitchenware on fire
My flow delicious-like sweet and sour pork
I do what I want I've got way more nerve than you
All that doubt about me?
Completely absurd
I coach my own life, I'm my own damn mentor
Watch the replay I score, then crack a smile
Leave an arc flying over your head
Don't be shocked that's just my daily routine
What kind of god shows up so down to earth?
High-ranked, yet so close to the beasts on the roof
Descends to the mortal world-yet still acts restless
Did Heaven change its rules now gods can catch feelings?
That compass of yours so bright, such fancy design
Looks just like the one I lost too familiar to miss
Thanks for bringing it back to the rightful owner today
No need to wear it round your neck don't want rope marks all over
Whoa whoa-buddy, what's running through your mind?
You dare try to take what's clearly mine?
Smelling jealous cause they all orbit me, huh?
Chill out who's the one with the crown on their head?
That new ride must've cost you a pretty penny, huh?
Then why's it look like it's parked in the trash?
Leading the way in style-got your bros with me
Roll with me, maybe life won't suck so bad
Looks like he's on cloud nine
Master cat, you're gonna put wrinkles on my face!
My nose I is not a slide.
Oh, I have hypo allergenic skin!
I brewed this peach daiquiri myself
You simply must try it
3000 years to flower
3000 years to ripen
If you drink it
You'd be fit as a fiddle,
And forget all your sorrows
If you can brew such a dope elixir
How come I never got a taste?
It's not heavenly peach, silly?
It's just regular one
Mixed With catnip
We makes him sleepy
And then finally the Compass will be ours
Please, master cat
I see you brought back with the lil' snack
Come, Bro
Let me top you up there
Such fragrance!
I must resist.
Rat, rat, rat-a-tat...
Rat, rat, rat-a -tat...
Don't you dare bully my rats
Batty brats, learned your lesson yet
Do your homework on me
Your turn..
You must be starving
I saved you a peach cake.
Have a nibble.
Buddy, I get your frustration
I'm here for you
I won't let anyone bully you anymore
Come,
Time to go home.
Ride the crosswind
I'm the big cheese
Go where the wind blows
Lift Off!
You're one of us now
Come here.
We're all part of the rat race
Ah, I can see you're a pro too
I know a rat when I smell one
It took years to amass this collection
Ancient civilizations had their glory
But they have been long forgotten
Those who forge history anew
Are brainy game changers like us
Do you know
What Golden City needs
You!
You and Your mega brain
Unfortunately, geniuses like us
Are always Fate's plaything
Fate always targets our Achilles' tail
Fate always targets our Achilles' tail.
Like you, I once. had a dream
Until 300 years ago...
Too slow, you're far too slow.
Hey little lizard.
Chase me if you can
Feel the power of the Astral Compass
Help!
My eyes hurt.
The tail...
My tail!
A mere blunder
Made my eyes unable to see daylight
I was forced underground, to scheme in the dark
Luckily, I discovered this
I tried to use it to locate the Astral Compass
Only in our hands
Can the Compass' true power be harnessed
We were one step from reaching our dream
But that dumb cat got its dirty paws on it.
And became a phony god
You were the one who found it first
I'm gonna help you
Take back
The Astral Compass
No need for self-doubt
We worked until burnout
Our genius is overlooked
Cos they have Heaven's playbook
Once we get the Compass
We'll be no one's doofus
Gargoyles Squad
I hope you all rot
We'll stage a coup d'etat
Mega Rat, Mega Rat
Stay tuned for our victory
We'll sure rewrite history
I bet he'd love this prezzie
Bottoms up, buddy!
It's time
For the Lantern Festival
To begin!
This is so lit.
Hold your horses
The best is yet to come
Master
The VIP seats are ready
We don't just let any alley cat in
Get ready!
Holiness
Brace yourself
Your Holiness,
Did you light up the city's outskirts?
Why can't you bring it up later?
Sonny, where did that lantern float come from?
Do they Have paperwork?
Reporting Master!
There's no record of it
Then shut the gates
Don't let it in
The gates are shut
Bruh, look at how he struts
We want your autograph!
Whoa, a Holy Cat float!
It's ginormous!
It's the GOAT!
It's divine!
Never seen such a majestic float before
What a stunning sight!
Only the Holy Cat could have such a float!
Could it be...?
Shadow puppets?
How bougie!
You fake.
The compass belongs to me!
Rattalion, hoist him up
Let our Lil' Bro have his pay back.
How dare you crash into my float!
Sonny and Xander
Go see what's going on
Yes sir.
Lil' Bro,
He's my real prezzie for you
Hey, what are you doing?
Don't you want your pay back?
String the traitor up
Yes, boss!
Retreat!
Things are getting outta hand.
We are the sacred gargoyles.
We can't just stand by and do nothing
They opened their eyes
Gone in a flash.
Who tied you up?
How did you hang in there?
My float!
You opened the city gate to intruders.
Ruined the festivities
And brought harm to the citizens
What is your wicked ploy?
The Compass!
Where has it gone?
How come you've lost it?
It's a total train wreck
Weren't you sent from Heaven to save us?
How did things end up like this?
Looks like he's not a real deity
Heavenly objects are indestructible
Master, there are footprints here
Looks like rats'
I smell a rat...
That's it
Lil' Feeney
That rat's got his claws on the Compass
Let's go after him.
So what if the cat lost the Compass?
The cat was never the rightful owner.
It's a vital instrument from Heaven
Possessing infinite power.
If it ever fell into evil hands,
All hell will break loose
Guard Gold City with your lives
Yes sir!
I don't care if you're a deity or not.
But you shouldn't be a phony
You've betrayed me
World dominion was withing.
Our grasp!
Be afraid, be very afraid.
Can you feel the heat?
Too late for regrets
This is the landmark of Gold City
Ao Jiao Palace.
Astral Compass.
Activate!
What?
How come?
Tell me what's wrong
Didn't you defeat my night demon with it?
You must know how to activate it.
Tell me, tell me your trick
I got it!
It's this gizmo
Don't stop!
The day has finally come
For Mega Rat.
To take over the world
This isn't right
Our bustling festival
Has been totally wrecked
These monsters are way too fierce
Not even Holy Cat can handle this
Where the hell did these baddies come from?
Evil can't beat the righteous
Sooner or later, we clean them up
Kitty! Kitty!
My best friend got taken by the Evil Rat
Please save him.
You're our superhero!
Kitty, keep it up!
Master hasn't returned.
Let's go find him
If we wait long enough, he'll be  back
We need to guard the city
Yup, Do what master says.
You only do as you're told.
Are you gutless or heartless?
Huh, you troublemaker.
Now what?
I've put up with you long enough
Just beat it.
You wanna save your friend?
All by yourself?
Master always told us to do the right thing
Even he has the courage to save his friend.
Aren't we brave enough to help him?
Should I stay put?
No more!
Hey you, need a ride?
You'll never get there I by foot
Buckle up. Hold tight.
Off we fly.
Something's off.
Oh no, Master fell
Master!
What do you mean he ''fell' ?
He is KAPUT!!!
I don't kaput!
I'm immortal.
I'm just inside the mousetrap,
Chillaxing.
Didn't I tell you to guard Purple Gold Temple?
Why flock here?
Jade couldn't hold back anymore
Hurry back to Gold City.
And stand guard at Purple Gold Temple
Copy that.
Take care, Master.
Let's go.
Oh no, please don't go!
Get us outta here first
Copy that.
We lost one more to the trap
I was caught off guard.
Hey, what's he doing here?
He came to save his friend
Friend?
Do scammers have friends?
It's too dangerous here
You guys must leave quickly
We're worried about you
We can't leave you behind like this
Gargoyle Squad reporting to duty.
We await your orders, Master
You're getting in my way!
The enemy has declared war.
Charge!
Back up!
Hold it.
Sheesh,
Scoot your buns to your saddles
Lil' jocks, start to pedal
Spin your way to an ace future
And even get a toned figure
Step on it, clench that rear
Kick into highest gear.
Your heart's the generator
Love's our electric power
One, two, three, four..
Five, six, seven, eight..
Get your wheels a spinning
The cycle  paths are a coming
Commander,
We have an intruder.
Those wussy Gargoyles
It's about time
I'll kick their glazed tile butts
Watch me pull off a pageant
Of science and magic power.
Wait!
Watch out for traps.
Why is he so rashed?
Oh, there is a bomb inside
Mega Rat reigns at last!
What's this?
Yeet!
This smoke is weird
Stay alert
Let's run that way!
That's the pipsqueak he wants to save
Disperse!
Darn it, I've lost my powers!
Why am I suddenly wiped?
That smoke must be poisonous
Remember me?
Phoenix Master the warrior god.
Who the hell are you?
Enough of your dirty tricks
You haven't changed at all.
200 Years Ago
The Great Phoenix Master.
This humble mouse
Dreams of becoming a Gargoyle
Protecting Gold City with my inventions
Teammates, check this out.
This is Thunder Smokescreen
It explodes if trespassers step on it
Multi angled Surveillance Goggles
Allows you to scope out every  direction
This contraption is even cooler
Powered by a magnetic crystal.
Dodgy stunts
Only good for fooling kids
Dodgy stunts?
Chicken herder,
Feel the power of my "stunts" !
The Astral Compass!
Time for my payback
Master!
Bruh.
What does being a caged beast feel like?
You'll never get out of my traps alive
My precious Compass!
Catch them!
Yes sir!
Think you can escape?
Don't let them get away
Go after them!
Catch them!
Over there!
Don't run!
Block him from both sides
Two pronged attack!
Think you can escape?
We gotta get off my butts too
The compass is over there!
Game over
And yet,
C'est la vie.
Let it go.
Drift with the clouds.
Que sera, sera.
Oops, what am I blabbering about?
You guys didn't see nothin
Attack!
Yes, sir
Lil' Feeney, you slayed it!
I only laid an egg
Gee, he's floating upwards
You lay killer eggs.
Pop them out and clobber them
Killer
I'm dope.
Bruh,
I need to feel more stress
Feeney, you're our only hope
If you don't pop'em eggs
We'll have egg on our faces
Nice try egging me on
Don't push yourself too hard.
Yeah, no big deal even if we all go kaput.
No way! I don't wanna go kaput.
I can't chicken out!
Gotta get one up  on them.
Pop!
Let it go!
Drift with the clouds
Pop!
This makes me feel so 'laid' back
Let it go!
Drift with the clouds
Be... careful.
You traitor!
Way to go, Feen.
This makes me feel so 'laid' back.
Let it go!
Que sera, sera.
The exit is over there
Hold tight.
Xander, we didn't go kaput after all
That looks like...
The Astral Compass.
Oh gosh.
I'm eternally grateful.
Gold City will be safe from now on.
Yay, our city is safe
Gold city is safe.
Now that I'm leaving so soon,
I'm missing this place already.
Me too
Master!
We finally did good by Gold City
At last, we'll rise in Heaven's esteem
That's for sure.
You guys earned huge  brownie points
Bruh will reward you for this
Just wait and see
Proves we need to stick our necks out at times
Proves we need to stick our necks out at times.
Else we'll lose the chance to prove our worth
Divided we fall,
United, we stand.
Phoenix Master
You tried to fight the night demon.
Abused your magic power,
Endangering the mortals,
And even lost the Astral Compass
You are hence banished to Earth
To be patron of Purple Gold Temple
And guardian of Gold City
Till you recover the Astral Compass
And reach enlightenment
Then you can return to Heaven
To be reinstated as a warrior god.
Your deadline is 300 years.
Jade, always the star pupil.
Rehearsing your lines, eh?
Which opera tune is this?
The lyrics. make me feel uneasy.
You must be pooped
Let's go back and recharge
Master!
So the Compass was your ticket back to Heaven.
Are you leaving us behind?
You weren't assigned here
You got demoted
Master.
Why weren't you honest with us?
I've only been here 300 years
Haven't got round to explaining yet
Plus, I'm originally from Heaven
What's wrong with being homesick?
So that's it?
You're never coming  back?
He'll look out for you wherever he is
I can champion for you guys in Heaven,
So the sky's the limit.
What's not to like?
Hmm, I thought
We had a whale of a time together.
Here, we're nothing but roof squatters.
Who doesn't want to climb to the top?
Only losers slide down the ladder.
Are you okay with being dissed
As roof beasts?
He was just venting
Don't take it to heart
Sonny, your dad the Dragon King
Is best buddies with Master.
He always has your back
Xander, you're an upstanding guy.
He trusts you
To get the job done.
Jade, Master is most fond of you
He raised you
like his own child.
Lil' Feeney,
Time's up.
Let's get going.
You'll find red packets on the roof.
It's lucky money from bruh
By seven stars and energy divine
The Big Dipper rises and shines
Heavenly passage
Open wide!
Feeney, we're home at last!
My Lord, I offer you the real Astral Compass
Bruh, wake up!
Bruh.
Wake up already!
Whereare we ?
Aren't we back in Heaven?
The Celestial Master said we're not enlightened
We were flicked back to Earth again
Feeney, what time is it?
Just past midnight
That's impossible
Where's the Compass?
Take a look.
There must've been a mix-up
It's not yet midnight
Bruh!
By seven stars and energy divine
The Big Dipper rises and shines
Heavenly passage.
Open wide!
Heavenly passage, open
Wide!
We still have a shot
Heavenly passage, open wide!
Heavenly passage, open wide.
Bruh!
What are you doing, Feeney?
You're blocking my way back to Heaven
Time's up. We missed it already
Says who?
It's over.
C'mon, don't fight it
My Lord,
I retrieved the Compass
Why am I still barred from Heaven?
I'm already a deity,
Aren't I already enlightened?
You lousy Compass.
I've searched for you for 300 years
300 darn years!
Chill, Bruh.
You don't even work!
Useless! Useless!
Be gone!
Well, this ain't so bad.
Not weighed down by deity duty
Exactly,
Let it go.
Drift with the clouds.
Hey, the fireworks were awesome this year.
Phoenix Master.
You know me, I'm. Gold Tooth!
The richest man in town.
Sorry, that's not me
You got the wrong person
No way!
You're totally the Phoenix Master.
Please don't bring it up
I'm not a deity anymore
You really thought you're a deity?
What else do you think he is?
Our friendly neighbor
The good neighbor who sets off fireworks for us every year!
So long, folks.
Goodbye.
One more cup,
Then I'll be gone
You can't leave us.
Grew up watching your fireworks
Who else can take over from you?
We toil away for a whole year
So we can see your fireworks
They are Gold City's favorite tradition
Stay and open a fireworks shop here
I'll bankroll it.
Totally.
If you were gone
New Year celebrations won't be the same
How about "Friendly Neighbor Fireworks"?
Yay! "Friendly Neighbor Fireworks" it is.
To "Friendly Neighbor Fireworks"!
Neighbor?
What demon is that?
Bruh, we are nobodies now
Nobodies?
Out of the way, pests!
The Purple Gold Temple is under attack
Follow me! Jade.
Hold your fire.
Save our own skins first
Go for it. Charge!
Just do your part as Gargoyles.
And crouch on the roof.
It's a war zone out there
What can it be?
Big Yikes!
Look, Mommy!
It's that cat!
It's Holy Cat!
Holy Cat!
Cat and mouse team
They shouldn't risk their lives for us
You vermin!
It's showtime. When I'm done
You won't have roofs to squat on
Master!
It's burning
Afraid now, huh?
Citizens,
I've lied to you for 300 years
I'm so sorry
Feeney,
Bruh
Today,
We'll make good on a false promise
Even if it took 300 years
Phoenix master
Mega Rat-ta-tat, I'm the big cheese
I'm the warrior god
Who rides a phoenix
Turns out Master is the legendary warrior god?
What a hunk!
I haven't lost my mojo at all
Still looking good after all these years
Help!
Huh, it's you!
Master, watch your back
Master! He is scared of the light.
His eyes can't stand the light.
The compass!
Give it back to me
C'mon, spit it out!
Dream on
Great talisman,
Turn!
Feeney!
Kapow!
No! My Purple Gold Temple!
Our home.
Run!
Let go of the Gargoyles!
Stay where you are
Not a step forward
I'll smash them to smithereens
Stop, wait!
What do you want?
As a super villain,
Gotta make the most shameless
Despicable demand
If you do what I say
I'll spare the Gargoyles
Don't listen to him, Master
Shut up, you little critters
Monster!
Ew, gross
Tell me what you want
Get on your knees, for starters
Master!
Then,
Crawl to me respectfully
With a straight face
And proper posture.
Oh no, Master!
Now you know how it feels to be trampled
You surrender?
Yes, or no?
If not, I'll stomp on you till you die.
Hey, my bad.
I suddenly recall
That I'm immortal
Sorry you stomped for nothing.
Are you winding me up?
Wait,
I have an idea
Celestial Master
Heck, who?
My Lord, please show up
Poor Master, he's lost his mind.
Bottle Deity,
Not Bottle, Phoenix
Whoopsy-daisy. Phoenix Master,
Are you ready?
Here's the Astral Compass
Please check it out.
I get the cut of your jib.
Wait for me
Bruh,
Don't you dare leave me out of it
You can't shoulder this alone
Feeney
In the next life,
I want us to be pals again
Yes, bros forever
Geez, Feeney's lost it too
Darn the light
Your lightning bolt is too weak.
It's barely scratching me
Come again!
Can't feel a thing
No pain!
Wow, look at the new fireworks this year
Beautiful
The God of Fireworks.
Darned light
Oh my eyes!
You can't just go kaput!
Master!
Quick, come help!
They're stuck under the debris
It's an emergency
Sonny, hang in there
Doesn't hurt at all
Is that all you've got, old man in the sky?
I feel. nothing.
Gimme more!
I can't take any more bolts
Celestial Master,
You're a wimp
Gods please help us!
Master!
Ow, that missed my face
What?
Now it's your turn
Citizens
The light?
The light is upon us!
You bastard!
I'm gonna take you down with me
You old' chicken-herder
If I go, you're all coming with me
Put them down.
Pipsqueak turncoat
Think you can run from me?
Hands off!
Good neighbors.
Now's the time
To send light back.
Let's refract light back to the Gods
Shoot!
Aim the light at his eyes
The light's too scattered
Use the temple's light tower
There'll be no temple left.
We have no choice
Go for it!
My dear neighbors
Aim over there!
Aim it at Purple Gold Temple
Peel his eyes open, Master!
Killed by my own kind
Consider it an honor.
Good job
My superpowers!
I got you back at last
My precious.
We won
Golden City is saved!
What are you gonna do to me?
Careful not to break this nifty device
Can you explain how it works?
Yep.
It's yours.
In that case, we're even.
Give us fireworks...oops,
I mean Warrior God.
Master!
Aww, you're making me blush.
Warrior God has finally reached enlightenment.
Your deeds have redeemed you and return to Heaven with honor.
Your position is restored...
Master!
Are you leaving now?
My Lord, I need more time
Sonny, Xander,
Look out for Jade
Always stand on guard for Gold City.
Actually, I've decided...
Hey, I haven't finished yet
Master!
He's gone.
He just went kaput snap! gone in a flash.
What have you decided on?
You left us guessing the second half.
Xander,
How come you're swollen?
Celestial Master
For 300 years,
I haven't been honest
Now, I gotta speak from they heart.
Say what you want
I've decided not to return to Heaven
Gold City is where I belong
It's where my duty lies
Approved.
Heaven doesn't have earth's fireworks
Master!
These are red packets from Master
Yay, we're rich.
Huh, what's this?
"Sonny"
" After I'm gone"
Don't ever forget
"You're the son of the Sea Dragon,"
Not some lousy loach
Walk tall even without horns
"Xander,"
'You're a straight arrow"
Who loves to kick evil's butt
But you always run your mouth
Like a firecracker.
Learn to think
Before you speak
Stay the course,
And life will be rewarding
I'll show you I'm no crackpot.
Crackerjack!
Jade, here's yours
Jade,
You always. remain true to your heart
Even-after returning to Heaven
I'll continue to learn from you.
Let's kick butt at our jobs
We are both in the guardian business
Ensuring safety is most important.
Please, he's just blowing hot air
What's "Ensuring safety"
He's just a security guard?
We should seize the Compass
So we can still hang out here as heroes
Oh there's a red packet for Ten ten too
Ten- ten, you move so fast
That you forget who you are
And where you're headed.
Don't lose yourself on the journey
That reminds me, Master.
Where's Ten-ten gone?
Did you run into him in Heaven?
Oh yeah,
Maybe he's gone kaput. Oh no.
He went for reinforcements from Heaven
So why isn't he back yet?
Didn't see him in Heaven.
That brat.
Hope he didn't get lost.
Co...Compass.
Thanks for leading me to enlightenment.
Let the Compass
Fulfill its destiny.
Master!
Ten-Ten
People are strange in Heaven.
They speak in a weird way
And they made me wear this cap
We missed you like crazy!
I jumped through so many hoops to get back.
Who are those two?
Wait, where's the demon?
Where's the evil dragon?
Goodbye.
Farewell.
Left without a word.
Come back for pear blossom season
Godspeed!
Safe travels.
Welcome back to the real world, friend this ain't Tom and Jerry.
Still need that childhood hope to keep your back straight
No matter how stormy it gets, I will never delay
I'm boarding the dream-chasing flight it'll taker off on time
Cause I know I can get the future I aim for
Not giving up-that's my secret
When I close my eyes, it's her smile and lashes I see
When I'm about to break, she's the cure for me
I've got to protect her like Jerry guards his cheese
Got her a parachute 'cause we're flying too high
Go on adventures, finding treasure in caves
I counter their every move guess they don't have enough tricks
Even when Tom falls in love,
He can also rap like Ma Siwei
Compass shining on the chest,
Wanna.be with her, want every night to be Mid-Autumn
Sit on the moon boat she's gonna make me handsome.
Through wind and rain, you carry the weight
I'll take you back to the childhood home deep in your heart
Turn on the TV-Tom and Jerry's always there
No matter,how life goes- don't forget to smile.
The sun's about to.set-five minutes ' 'til school's out.
Wanna hop quick onto dad's bike, sit on the back
Turn on the TV-Tom and Jerry's always around
Tomorrow will be better-please don't forget to smile
Landed in the East, a dragon flies overhead
The world I see, you don't, need to understand
I can swallow the hardship myself, don't need your comfort
I know I ain't a basic cat-. don't need your fake commend
My merch out-there-take a spin, check the scene
All the real talents you can name are standing with me
Sick of yesterday spalace today I want a new suite
Living like a god taking life day by day
When I almost lost my way, she came and made me see
No one can decide for me how, to live this life
Fighting the dark-our,friendship's bond won't break apart
I'm born to be the lead-not here for a cameo
:
Hearts as one can break gold an old Chinese line
We share blessings and hardship taste it all, sweet and bitter
The scene flips in a blink from 2D to 3D
Thank to you my dream team the success we build is sealed
Through wind and rain, you carry the weight
I'll take you back to the childhood home deep in your heart
Turn on the TV-Tom and Jerry's always there
No matter how,life goes-don't forget to smile
The sun's about to set five minutes 'til school's out
Wanna hop quick onto dad's bike, sit-on the back
Turn on the TV Tom and Jerry's always around
Tomorrow will be better please don't forget to smile